Byron Tunnell Papers, Inclusive: 1925-1999, undated, Bulk: 1961-1999
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
Byron Tunnell Papers
Inclusive: 1925-1999, undated, Bulk: 1961-1999
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials http://www.baylor.edu/lib/bcpm/
43
Tunnell, Byron, 1925 - 2000
28 document boxes and 3 oversized boxes.
This collection consists of the personal and public papers of a long-time Texas public servant, Byron Tunnell. Records include awards and certificates, biographical materials, campaign materials, correspondence, legislation, photographs, speeches, and press files accumulated throughout his career.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
Byron M. Tunnell was born on October 14, 1925, in Tyler, Texas. He was educated in the Tyler public school system and attended Tyler Junior College. Following military service in the Naval Air Corps during World War II, Tunnell attended Baylor University where he earned a law degree in 1952. Tunnell then returned to his hometown of Tyler and served as an assistant district attorney before entering private practice. In 1959, Bob Bullock, future Texas Comptroller and Lieutenant Governor, joined the practice. Tunnell and Bullock developed a close friendship over the next forty years, sharing a passion for public service to their native Texas. When Bullock passed away in 1999, Tunnell delivered one of two eulogies at the funeral.
Tunnell was active with the Junior Chamber of Commerce (Jaycee’s) and by the 1950's turned his attention toward politics. He was elected to serve in the Texas House of Representatives from 1956 to 1965 and was appointed Speaker of the House from 1963 to 1965 by his peers. A second term as Speaker was projected, but to the surprise of many, Tunnell joined the Texas Railroad Commission in 1965. His tenure with the Railroad Commission coincided with the energy crisis of the early 1970's which led to his collaboration with the Interstate Oil Compact Commission.
On September 15, 1973, Tunnell resigned from the Railroad Commission to become a vice-president and lobbyist for Tenneco Inc., an oil and gas company based in Houston. In the 1990's, Tunnell returned to public service, first as a member of the Board of Trustees for the Employee Retirement System of Texas, and then as a member of the State Conservatorship Board. He was appointed by George W. Bush as a co-conservator to overhaul the struggling Texas Commission on Alcohol and Drug Abuse.
Tunnell died of cancer at his home in Lake Palestine, Texas, on March 7, 2000.
Scope and Content
The timeline of the Byron Tunnell papers begins in the early 1950's and concludes in 1999, shortly before his death. Materials in the collection depict his years of public service, primarily as a member and Speaker in the Texas House of Representatives and later as Texas Railroad Commissioner. Additional materials related to his time as Vice President of Tenneco, Inc., are also housed in this collection, as well as items from his appointments to the Employee Retirement System and State Conservatorship Board.
Tunnell's papers are arranged in eleven series and include awards, certificates, biographical materials, campaign materials, correspondence, legislation, photographs, and press files.
Series 1. Appointments covers the positions to which Tunnell was assigned duties later in life. As a member of the Employee Retirement System and State Conservatorship Board, he created reports, commissions, funding manuals, newsletters, clippings, and other materials. Series 2. Campaign materials, which are arranged chronologically, include Tunnell’s races for the Texas House of Representatives (1956-1964) and for the Railroad Commission (1966-1972).
Series 3. Correspondence includes topical and personal letters, including some from Tunnell’s friend and former law partner, Lieutenant Governor Bob Bullock. Series 4. Court Cases highlights Tunnell’s appearance in the U.S. Supreme Court for the 1958 case Hawkins v. United States as well as other cases from the 1990's.
Materials in Series 5. Elected Positions are divided according to Tunnell's service on the Railroad Commission and in the Texas House of Representatives. Tunnell was Railroad Commissioner from 1965 to 1973 during an energy crisis, therefore, the materials are primarily focused on topics such as oil and gas. The Texas House of Representatives Subseries is divided according to each legislature and includes administrative files, correspondence, commemorative legislation, publications, and topical materials.
Series 6. Events chronicle Tunnell's attendance at banquets, luncheons, receptions, conferences, conventions, and several Texas inaugurations. The Lobbyist Series reflects Tunnell’s experiences at Tenneco, Inc., an oil and gas company based in Houston. The series includes awards and certificates presented to Tunnell, travel itineraries, guestbooks, day planners, political cartoons, and other related items.
Series 9. Photographs ranges in date from 1935 to 1999, and documents personal and business moments throughout Tunnell's life. Campaign headshots, golf outings, Christmas photos, and several hunting and fishing trips are represented. The Press Series includes news clippings and newsletters from Tunnell’s career. Series 11. Speeches includes nearly 200 speeches given by Tunnell, including a eulogy for Lieutenant Governor Bob Bullock. These items, dated 1961-1999, kept in Tunnell's original order, highlight the number of organizations and individuals he was involved with during his life.
Arrangement
The Byron Tunnell papers have been processed previously. The first instance concluded with no inventory or finding aid for the collection. In 2013, the papers were organized and described by Debbie Todd utilizing many existing folder titles in two series with multiple subseries each.
The current finding aid has further divided the papers into eleven series, several with subseries and sub-subseries. The eleven series are: 1. Appointments, 2. Campaigns, 3. Correspondence, 4. Court Cases, 5. Elected Positions, 6. Events, 7. Lobbyist, 8. Personal, 9. Photographs, 10. Press, and 11. Speeches.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to the W. R. Poage Legislative Library in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 43. Acquired 2007-07-10
Related Resources
Related references
Kohout, Martin Donell. "Tunnell, Byron M.," Handbook of Texas Online (http://www.tshaonline.org/handbook/online/articles/ftu32), accessed December 02, 2013. Published by the Texas State Historical Association.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Bullock, Bob -- Correspondence.; Tunnell, Byron, 1925-2000.
Subjects (Organizations)
Railroad Commission of Texas -- Records and documents.; Tenneco Inc -- Records and documents.; Texas. Legislature. House of Representatives. Office of the Speaker -- Records and documents.
Subjects
Lawyers -- Texas -- Archives.; Legislators -- Texas -- Archives.; Petroleum industry and trade--Texas.; Political campaigns --Texas--Archives.; Political cartoons.
Genres
Awards.; Certificates.; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Correspondence.; Ephemera.; Guest books.; Handbooks and manuals.; Invitations.; Itineraries.; Legal documents.; Legislative materials.; Newsletters.; Photographs.; Records (Documents); Reports.; Speeches.
- Appointments, 1991-1998; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  In addition to serving as a legislator and lobbyist, Byron Tunnell was appointed to several positions. He served on the Board of Trustees for the Employee Retirement System and on the State Conservatorship Board as co-conservator of the Texas Commission on Alcohol and Drug Abuse. This series, dated 1991-1998, includes reports, commissions, funding manuals, newsletters, clippings, resignations, and other materials. Each subseries is organized chronologically and are in good condition.
  - Employee Retirement System, 1991-1998; 1
    - Congratulations, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Oath of Office, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Service Credit, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Financial Disclosures, 1991-1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Growth Portfolios, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Travel Expenses, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Legislative Retirement Benefits, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Anniversary, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Report, “ERS of TX, 1947-1997” (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Retiree Raises, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - State Conservatorship Board, 1995-1998; 2
    - Commission, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Funding Manual, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Funding Requests, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - News Clippings, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Newsletter, New View, Vol. 5, No. 5, 1995 December (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Organizational Structure, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Report, Sixty Day Reports #1-6, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Report, “Senate/House Joint General Investigating Committee on TCADA”, 1995 October 17 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Resignation, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Campaigns, 1958-1973, undated; 2
  Series 2. Campaigns, dated 1958-1973, documents Byron Tunnell’s political campaigns for public office including the Texas House of Representatives and the Texas Railroad Commission. Materials include correspondence, brochures, newspaper clippings, administrative documents, and advertisements. This series is arranged chronologically by year and is in good condition.
  - Railroad Commission, 1965-1973, undated; 1
    - Re-Election Announcement, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Re-Election Poster, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Itinerary, 1965 March 10-14 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - General, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Administrative, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Biography, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - County Chairmen Memos, 1966 February-April (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Newspaper Clippings (1 of 4), 1966 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Newspaper Clippings (2 of 4), 1966 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Newspaper Clippings (3 of 4), 1966 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Newspaper Clippings (4 of 4), 1966 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Opposition, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Press Release, 1966 April 6 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Support, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Vote Totals by County, 1966 May 7 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - General, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Advertising, 1972, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 10)
    - Advertising, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Ballot Certification, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Biography, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Editorials, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Support, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Swearing In, 1973 January (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Texas House of Representatives, 1958-1964, undated; 2
    - Campaign Advertisements, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Flotorial Representative, undated (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 16)
    - Flotorial Representative, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Radio Advertisement Recording, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - State Representative (1 of 2), undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - State Representative (2 of 2), undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Congratulations, Price Daniel, 1958 September 16 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Brochure, “Re-Elect Byron Tunnell”, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Primary Candidates List, 1960 May 2 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - General, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1964 February-March (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - “A Special Evening on Byron Tunnell”, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1961-1995; 3
  Series 3. Correspondence includes personal and topical letters that were received by Byron Tunnell from 1961 to 1995. Several entries are included from Bob Bullock who was a business partner and close friend. The series is arranged alphabetically and is in good condition.
  - Absentee Ballot Request, 1966-1970 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Bullard, Ted, 1962-1971 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Bullock, Bob, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Bullock, Bob, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Bullock, Bob, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Bullock, Bob, 1972-1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Bullock, Bob, Fundraiser, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Bullock, Bob, Fundraiser, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Bullock, Thomas, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Capitol Information Service, 1983-1987 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Carr, Waggoner, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Congratulations, Railroad Commission Chairmanship, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Connally, John, 1963-1971 March (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Connally, John, Secretary of Treasury, 1971 October-November (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Cory, Dick, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Crawford, O.R., 1962-1966 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Creighton, Tom, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Crosier, Donald, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Daniel, Price, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Davis, Cliff, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Dies, Jr., Martin, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Ehrle, Will, 1962-1966 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Ellred, Roy, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Family (1 of 2), 1960-1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Family (2 of 2), 1960-1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - General, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - General, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - General, 1970-1995 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Greeting Cards, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Heard, Wyatt, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Heatley, W.S., 1962-1966 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Hooper, Don, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Jaycees, 1954-1958 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Johnson, Robert E., 1966-1970 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Jones, Jerome, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Kennedy Assassination, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Kuecheinmeister, Fred, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Land Purchase, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Law Practice, 1961-1964 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Loftis, Harry, 1963-1969 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Loftis, Harry, Boy Scouts of America, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Loggins, Sim, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Mardock, Julian, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Marone, Joe, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Matrisciani, H.R., 1965 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Mays, Abe, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - McHenry, Ben, 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - McHenry, Ben, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Parse, Robert, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Resignation Letters, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - State Employees Retirement System, 1969-1973 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Texas State Historical Survey Committee, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Tyler Junior College, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Court Cases, 1952-1994; 4
  Series 4. Court Cases, which consists of materials from 1952 to 1994, includes documents related to Byron Tunnell’s legal practice. Materials such as court documents, contracts, newspaper clippings, and correspondence from his Supreme Court appearance in Hawkins v. United States is present as well as items from the Alfaro and George Green cases. This series is arranged chronologically and is in good condition.
  - Supreme Court, Admission Documents, 1952-1958 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Supreme Court, Hawkins v. U.S., 1958 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Alfaro Case, Bob Bullock, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Alfaro Case, Case Overview, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Alfaro Case, Dow Chemical, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Alfaro Case, Forum Non Conveniens Legislation, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Alfaro Case, Jobs for Texas, 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Alfaro Case, Texaco USA, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - George Green vs. Texas Department of Human Services, Court Documents, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - George Green vs. Texas Department of Human Services, Contract, 1993 May 10 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - George Green vs. Texas Department of Human Services, Clippings, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - George Green vs. Texas Department of Human Services, Correspondence, 1994 May-June (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - George Green vs. Texas Department of Human Services, Legislative Budget Board, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Elected Positions, 1957-1979, undated; 5
  Byron Tunnell served in the Texas House of Representatives from 1957 to 1965, and on the Texas Railroad Commission from 1965 to 1973. Both positions are documented in Series 5. Elected Positions.
  The Texas House of Representatives Subseries is further divided by the appropriate legislature. Representative Tunnell served during the 55th, 56th, 57th, and 58th State Legislatures and was elected Speaker of the House for his final term. Administrative files, correspondence, commemorative legislation, publications, and topical materials on subjects such as apportionment of state legislatures, PKU, education, and finances are included within the subseries. Items related to Tunnell's time as Speaker of the House are also present.
  The Railroad Commission Subseries is divided into two sub-subseries: General and Interstate Oil Compact Commission. The General Sub-subseries includes annual reports, correspondence, newsletters, and topical materials primarily concerning oil and gas. The Interstate Oil Compact Commission Sub-subseries contains meeting minutes, correspondence, and items related to several committees including Energy Resources, Environmental Affairs, and Environmental Protection Advisory Committees as well as the Resolutions Subcommittee. Each subseries is organized alphabetically and in good condition.
  - Texas House of Representatives, 1957-1965, undated; 1
    - 55th Legislature, 1957; 1
      - Commemorative Legislation, Family, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - Special Session, 1957 October-December (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Topical, Alcohol, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Topical, Franchise Tax, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Topical, Insurance, 1957 May (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - 56th Legislature, 1959-1960; 2
      - Address to Joint Session, Lieutenant General Bernard Schriever, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - Commemorative Legislation, Family, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, 1959 August (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - House Bill 108, Milk Fat, circa 1960 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Topical, Defense, 1959 May 5 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - 57th Legislature, 1960-1963, undated; 3
      - Administrative, Information Guide, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Administrative, Members Terms, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - Administrative, Pre-Legislative Conference, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - Commemorative Legislation, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence, Constituent, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence, General, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - Publication, The Texas Book, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      - Speaker Campaign, Announcement, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - Speaker Campaign, Congratulations, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - Speaker Campaign, Correspondence, Support, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - Speaker Campaign, Newsletter, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      - Speaker Campaign, Support, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - Speaker Campaign, Will Ehrle, 1961 March 22 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - Topical, Education, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 41)
      - Topical, Filing for Record Procedure, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 42)
      - Topical, Judicial, Appeals, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - Topical, Judicial, Suits, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 44)
      - Topical, Loans, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 45)
      - Topical, Taxes, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Topical, Transportation, Farm-to-Market Roads, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - 58th Legislature, 1960-1965; 4
      - Adjournment, 1963 May 24 (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Commemorative Legislation, Family, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Committee Appointments and Requests, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Committee Requests, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, General, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, General, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, Grover, Henry, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, Harris, O.H. “Ike”, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, Hendryx, Gene, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, Hughes, Robert, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Isaacks, Maud, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, LaValle, Peter, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Murray, Menton, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, Mutscher, Gus, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, Nugent, James, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, Parker, Carl, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, Pool, Joe, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, Prentice, George R., 1964 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, Purcell, Graham, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, Ramey, Thomas, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, Rogers, Walter, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, Texas Legislative Council, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, Tower, John, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Existing Rules, 1962 December (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Guest Register, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Honorary Commission, Texas Ranger, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Installation Program, Speaker, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - Opening Session, 1962 December (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - Publication, “1965 Legislative Program”, Texas Bar Journal, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - Publication, “House Journal”, 1963 April 24 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - Publication, “The Legislature: An Overview,” The Texas Observer, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - Resignation, 1965 January 8 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - Speaker’s Apartment Inventory, 1965 May (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Speaker Campaign, General, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - Speaker Campaign, Acceptance Speech, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - Speaker Campaign, Correspondence, Support, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - Speaker Campaign, Opposition, 1962 June (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - Speaker Campaign, Support, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Speaker Campaign, Support, 60th Legislature, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - Speaker’s Day, 1963 April 17 (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - Speaker’s Day, 1964 November 24 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - Special Election, 36th District, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - Standing Committees, 1961 August 8 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - Topical, Apportionment of State Legislatures, Bills and Population Maps, 1960-1964 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - Topical, Apportionment of State Legislatures, Clippings, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - Topical, Apportionment of State Legislatures, Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 45)
      - Topical, Apportionment of State Legislatures, Court Cases, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 46)
      - Topical, Apportionment of State Legislatures, National Commission on Constitutional Government, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 47)
      - Topical, Apportionment of State Legislatures, Southern Conference of the Council of State Governments, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 48)
      - Topical, Apportionment of State Legislatures, Testimonies, 1964 July 22 (Box 5, Folder 49)
      - Topical, Education, Special Education, 1963 July (Box 5, Folder 50)
      - Topical, Health, PKU, Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Topical, Health, PKU, Louisiana, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Topical, Health, PKU, Massachusetts, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)